essayhealth.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy – Easy Health

**essayhealth.com Privacy Statement**

**essayhealth.com’s Privacy Policy – An Overview**

essayhealth.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for all users of the internet as a whole and our web site in particular. All the sites owned and managed by our team have been included in this policy. This policy applies only to essayhealth.com and other websites which carry the our brand and not to other companies or organisation’s

**Web sites to which we link**

essayhealth.com values the privacy of our visitors and our members and takes many steps to protect their privacy. By visiting essayhealth.com’s website, or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.

**What this Privacy Statement Covers**

This Privacy Statement covers essayhealth.com’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that essayhealth.com gathers when you access essayhealth.com Sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the use of your Personal Information by third parties that essayhealth.com does not own or control, or to individuals that essayhealth.com does not control or manage.

**Links to Other Sites**

essayhealth.com Sites contains links to blogs and other websites that are not owned or controlled by essayhealth.com We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites.

**Information Gathering And Usage**

essayhealth.com is the sole owner of information collected on essayhealth.com Sites. We do not share or sell your information with anyone without your authorization or consent in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Statement.

**Registration**

You may provide us with certain information such as your name, email address, postal address when registering for certain services such as personalisation, chat, email, community pages, contests and promotions. This information will primarily be used for the purpose of providing personalisation and verification.

**Feedback**

Our site’s feedback form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age or income level).

We use customer contact information from the feedback form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by sending us an e-mail.

**Contests**

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), financial information (income bracket), and demographic information (like their zip code, age or income level).

We use contact data from our contestant to send information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The users contact information is also used by us to contact the visitor when necessary, primarily to announce new contests, contest results and site features.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

A User may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest organizer ( the website ) or the sponsor, in which the user identity is divulged to third party – as long as the user gives consent.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by sending us an e-mail.

**Electronic Newsletter**

The site offers a free electronic newsletter to its users. We gather the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by using the link provided in every newsletter.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. essayhealth.comuses cookies to track user traffic patterns and for the personalisation feature.

**Registration:-** When you register essayhealth.com uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. Cookies also enable you to enter the sites ad use services as a member without having to log on each time.

If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any essayhealth.com site.

**Choice/Opt-Out policy**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the user. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Statement is a living document. We will modify this document as we add new features to essayhealth.com. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. If we make material changes to our privacy policy we will post those changes to this Privacy Statement, the essayhealth.com homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web Site, you can contact :- essayhealth.com
